



# Summary

I am a Full-Stack Web Developer proficient in Vue, Typescript, React, Node, Express, and Postgresql. I have 2 years of experience as a professional software developer and 7 years of experience in customer service and sales. My diverse work experience has helped me develop advanced communication, teamwork, and problem-solving skills. It's my dream to develop technology that genuinely helps people on a daily basis.

# Relevant Work Experience

# **ZulaFly** - Software Developer

January 2021 - PRESENT

Established myself as an integral part of a small team of developers in my first months at ZulaFly.. With only three other developers in the company at the time of my hiring, I had to quickly learn Vue and a completely different tech stack than what I had learned in my boot camp. I soon moved from exclusively handling small bug fixes to implementing new features and mobile solutions.

After 6 months, I was trusted with handling UX/UI design and integration of new endpoints on the front end of our web-app. I work closely with the product owner, who has a better grasp on how the end-user interacts with the product, to implement and design new features that have a good balance of functionality and usability with a more modern UX design.

### Daily Duties:

- ⇒ Collaborate with cross-functional teams to design, develop, and maintain web and mobile applications.
- ⇒ Implement clean and efficient code using JavaScript, TypeScript, and C#.
- ⇒ Participate in the full software development lifecycle, from requirement analysis to deployment.
- ⇒ Conduct thorough testing and debugging to ensure the reliability and functionality of software applications.
- ⇒ Assist in optimizing application performance and resolving technical issues.
- ⇒ Work with version control systems (e.g., Git) to manage code repositories.
- ⇒ Meet with product owners and development team to design and develop new features and bug fixes

#### Tech Stack

Typescript, Vue, Vuetify, Vite, Xamarin.Forms, C#, MongoDB, SignalR, Azure

# Work Experience

#### JL Beers - Supervisor/Beertender

December 2015 - August 2022, Burnsville, MN

Quickly became an invaluable employee and was promoted to supervisor within the first year working there.

Developed multiple methods that are still used to complete a lot of daily tasks, everything from closing the store down quickly and effectively to spreadsheets that help split tips up and count down the safe.

#### **Boonya Systems** - Account Manager

July 2015 - December 2015, Bloomington, MN

Rebuilt company website, which is still being used, with a WordPress template that I modified to the best of my ability.

Built an email marketing campaign targeted at private practices focused on teaching them about HIPAA compliance as it relates to technology.

Lead multiple speaking engagements with private practice owners and managers teaching them how to better protect their patients sensitive information

### Radiate Digital - Account Executive

March 2014 - July 2015

The first full-time salesperson at a small web design/marketing company. The company was transitioning to selling custom-designed websites from the ground up at an affordable monthly price.

Acquired multiple big clients in my first couple of months, as well as multiple monthly based clients.

Learned the basics of web design and development, digital marketing, SEO, and more.

# Education

#### Thinkful - Full-Stack Engineering Flex

February 2020 - December 2020

JavaScript-based intensive program that teaches both front-end and back-end technologies, which enabled me to build an app from wireframe and design to building out the database.

# **Technical Skills**

Front-end

¡Query, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SASS, TypeScript, XML

Frameworks

Vue, Svelte, React, React Native, Express.js, Expo

Back-end

C#, Node.js, Postgresql, Heroku, Vercel, SQL, TypeScript, Kotlin

Dev Tools

Git, GitHub, Chrome Dev Tools, Postman, Google Analytics